screeps.com 2015-11-09

# Privacy Policy – Screeps Support Center

IP Chivchalov (hereinafter referred to as "We") through its online game Screeps collects personal and non-personal information about you that you provide in your account in order to provide and improve its services, but never hands this information to any third parties. We maintain all reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity and privacy of the personal information we collect.

While the security of your information is very important to us, and we take all reasonable precautions against possible breaches of our websites, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure. So, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe by memorizing your password or keeping it in a safe place.

We do not store our users' passwords in any way. We store only their hashes.

We do not collect any personal information from the payments you make on our websites. This is done solely by the third-party service provider Xsolla. You may read its Privacy Policy here: <http://xsolla.com/privacypolicy/>.

As most websites, we collect information automatically, and it is stored in the form of log files. This information includes such data as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, operating system, website activity, the number of "hits" a webpage is getting, and other relevant information which may be later combined with your personal and non-personal information.

We may use cookies, scripts, and other technologies to improve the use of our websites, products and services. You can disable or delete cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. We may use local storage to store content information and preferences of our users. We may collect certain "device-identifying data" about your personal computer or mobile device to create a digital identifier of your device in order to optimize our services for it.

Have more questions? Submit a request
